嗯，好的。 我
今天网速有点慢，但还是可以下载的。
一秒钟。
今天必须保持安静。   是的
。 大家好。
嗯，
这就是
Hello Ka
hello。
希望你们一切都好。 所以今天
我会尽量
保持安静。
因为我的室友正在睡觉，我
不想
太打扰他。 是的，我会尽量
保持安静。 所以，
即使我在说话，我喊一声也不会造成困扰。   请问
有人能告诉我音频质量如何吗？
我需要提升一下性能吗？还是直接
告诉我一声就行了？
我试试加装一个压缩机。
我有一个声音压缩器。 我只是这样做
。
嗯，很低。 好的。 我要把
输入源切换到我的调音台上
。
它在哪里？
在第二个
混音中。 好了，就是这样。 现在我的音频播放
很慢，听不清楚。 坚持，
稍等。
现在我的声音应该足够大，能被听到了吧
？
我稍等片刻，调整一下
音量。   好了
。 现在我应该声音更大一些。
我的麦克风音量似乎只有 27%。   我勒个去
？
嗯，
好的。  100%。
一切似乎都很顺利。 是的。
嗯，既然我能说话，我就
继续吧。
嗯，
今天我要玩一款
叫做《PU
冠军》的游戏。 在日本，它被称为 Pu
Peu Esports。
呃，
因为我身在日本，我的Steam
版本，我的Steam地区也是日本。
嗯，
我昨天才知道
这款游戏已经登陆 Nintendo Switch、
PS4 和其他主机平台，还有
Nintendo DS 平台。  DS平台
也有这款游戏。 是的。 所以，在
任天堂主机版本中，它
在日本和东亚地区被称为 Pew Pew Esports
。 但是，嗯，他们会的，嗯，
现在这种情况更普遍了。 所以从
某种意义上说，即使我在日本，我仍然可以
玩西方版本或
世界版本，嗯，还可以
与其他日本人以及
世界各地的音乐进行匹配。 所以，是的，我可以
和你们这些也有这玩意儿的人一起玩。   是的
。 嗯，
你真是个很会说悄悄话的人。
真的吗？ 我不知道。
嗯……那
我刚才说到哪儿了？
别以为我在小声说话。 我还在
说话。 我得少说话。
不，我比较安静。
我离麦克风很近。 所以，
嘿，你想耳语吗？ 耳语。 我可以
做到。
我可以关闭抑制功能。
我可以把它关掉。
我可以那样做，对吧？
好的。 我想你仍然可以从“
呃，现在怎么样了？”这个问题中听到一些声音。
这就像
玫瑰一样。
我的天啊。 是的，我觉得这就像是某种
声音。
我……
让我切换到游戏模式。 好的。
呃，如果你听到其他人
通过我的麦克风发出声音，请忽略它。
是我的室友。
嗯，你好。 对于那些在 YouTube 上
观看虾视频的人，
嗯，我想让你们……是的。 昨天有人
发现了这项服务。
嗯，
我找找看。 我需要添加这条
命令。
Stream snipe.com。
嗯，就是那个……
好吧，复制链接，然后去YouTube聊天。
我只需要正确粘贴一下就行了。
直播开始时间有点晚了
。
我的名字已被访问。
等等，我轻声细语的时候你听不见
。 什么？ 啊，找到了。 你能……
呃……为什么……为什么……为什么没有原声？
你听到了什么？ 哦。
兄弟，
那东西在哪儿？
我让你们等了好久。 对不起。 对不起。
一些技术问题。 即使 YouTube 已经关闭了视频剪辑功能，我仍然
希望人们能够从 YouTube 上剪辑视频
。 有一个
外部服务可以让
你进行剪辑。
稍等片刻。 我来调整一下。
等待。
呃，你可以在 YouTube 上制作一个感叹号视频
来解决这个问题。
好的。
让我们从游戏开始吧。
让我换一下。 哦，别在意。 嗯。
嗯。
我其实会打开游戏，然后设置好一些
东西，这样我就不用担心
设置之类的事情了。
嗯，
它有没有
宣布我现在正在直播？
没有，对吧？
让我来做这件事。 好的。
你能听到比赛的声音吗？
我相信你可以。
嗯，我可以看看评论吗？
我看不到评论。 你好。 菜单。
所以这款游戏基本上可以算作
动漫版的俄罗斯方块，某种程度上来说，我觉得它挺可爱的
。 这些其他的俄罗斯
方块，你可以说有 1、2、3、5 种
颜色。 呃，主要是四个。 这
取决于游戏模式。 如果游戏
模式有五种颜色，你就会看到五种这样的
颜色。
嗯。
哦，不是那个。
嘿。 嗯。
呃。 所以，今天我们只是进行
练习。
我们会这么做，
而且，
嗯，
我想做两个。 我愿意
。 好的，我们开始吧。 耐力。
等等，
这些就是噗哟噗哟里所有的角色了
。 我们找到了
Amit Ammy T Ringo。 她简直就像
个苹果。
那么，
他的名字该怎么发音呢？
琉伊·
莱娜·
艾莉·拉格纳斯。
这就是我今天要扮演的角色
。
呃，巫师德拉科·桑托雷斯。
呃，Rishu、Rishuka、
Carango、
黑暗王子、蝙蝠侠和 Alex。 我本来
想说是 Alex，不过嗯，差不多吧
。 你好。
我的耳机呢？ 嗯，
你能听到比赛的声音吗？ 是的，你能
听到比赛的声音，对吧？
你好。
呃，这是什么？
快速无人机从地球上起飞，然后降落。 我非常想要
那个
背景增益效果，
因为
啊，我都忘了
那简直就是俄罗斯方块了。
我完全不知道怎么玩这个游戏，
但是，是的，我们可以玩。
嗯，
我可以做到。 是的，
我可以做到。 是的。
呃，
啊，我本来不想做连锁的，
不过好吧。
啊，那是一条链子。 我不想那样做
。 为什么？ 他妈的。 没关系。 没关系。
呃，不，不，不。 我们可以解释顶部的情况。
没关系。
呃，
玩得越多，就越发现
白色的那些好像都是垃圾
。 嗯，对
，我只需要让它匹配，
然后让他们加入就行了。 就是这样。
呃，
我可能要输了。
呃，把它链起来。 不，
好的，这样可以。
哦，不。 我觉得我要死了。
哦，不。
什么？ 我们还有机会。
好的。 我们还有机会。 是的。 我们还有
机会。 你好。
我们还是有机会的。 我想我应该可以，
但
我说不出话来。 所以这就像一个
认知游戏。 是的。 但
我并非有意如此。 但我
（哭着）
做不到。
我意识到
Windows
有一个降噪功能，是AI自带的。
所以，还
等什么？
好的。
更胜一筹。   是的
。   是的
。 第一条链。 那很好。 那
很好。
我可以这样做。 好的。
我可以做到。
嗯，我可以砸碎
它，然后去那里，绿色的部分也可以去
那里。
嗯，能看出其中的联系。
我该怎么做？
这样也行。 呃，明白了。 好的，明白了
。 敞开心扉
。
我知道它在那里倒了。 好的。
打开并清理干净。
其实我觉得你那里应该还有空间。
呃，不不，
那
不是，
差不多了，
我有个想法，我可以做这个，可以做那个，然后把它
放在那里，和
它一起玩，然后我们做那个，把它
扔到那里。
我需要黄色的。
嗯，所以他们这样做，它
填补了空白，并且连接起来。
哦，
我需要学习如何计数。 我会
做计数，但我不知道怎么
做……
我不知道怎么做
直线之类的东西。
呃，链条，这就是我要找的词
。
外国佬：
呃，
我快死了。 我要死了。 我要死了。
新田。
哦，别这样杀了我。
求求你别那样杀了我。
哦，不。
我。
呃，所以
呃，
她有点……
哦，不。 不，不，不，不，不。
嗯，
我需要
什么？哦，那个？哦，等等。
我猜也是。
好的。
嗯，
好的。 照做。
哦，我第一次玩这个游戏，感觉
好复杂。
所以，
如果我足够专注，有时可以轻松完成三组链式动作。
但是我觉得发大财很难
。
你要记住，我是在和
电脑对战。
如果我是和真人一起玩，我
早就死了。
真正的人类问题。
来。
我可以清空场地吗？ 哦，是的。
我开始清理了。 没关系。
呃，
我今晚可以上场
。
呃，好的。
啊，不，不，没有弄错。
好的。 打，打，打。
哦，这可不好玩。 哦，不。
不，我已经死了。
[哭泣]
哦，YouTube聊天功能可以用了。
什么？
呃，它能
用吗？ 哦，它运行正常。
YouTube聊天功能正常。
目前的
运作方式有效吗？
啊，我死了。
玩游戏。
是啊，这游戏像是给
聪明人玩的，不像我。
我就是擅长玩FPS游戏之类的。   我就是那种不擅长玩烧
脑游戏的人。
[笑声]
嗯，
哦，对了，我好像要
参加一个噗噗噗锦标赛，
嗯，这个锦标赛是由 Vakone 主办的，
作为他们 Vakone
游戏节的一部分。 所以这是一场puyu vtuber clash
印度比赛锦标赛。
我不知道我的队友是谁，但我会
参加这场比赛，和
很多
擅长这场比赛的职业选手，或者
正在学习这场比赛的选手竞争。 我通过不断
练习才变得越来越厉害。 所以我想多加
练习，尽我所能做到最好。
什么是发烧？
我认为 Fever
更像是一家快节奏的
公司。   就是这样。
照做就是了。
嗯，没关系。   把
它清理干净。 我们可以把它清理干净。
它们
吃什么？
哦，那是两场
冲突了。 是的。
我说的没错。 嗯，
还有，
请告诉我这款游戏的拥有者是谁。
所以如果你想一起玩，请
在聊天中告诉我
。   我的
天哪。
[尖叫]
我的天哪。
呃，
然后
我
不知道为什么它让我感到不舒服。
哦，该死。
它也就
只能做到这些了。
不，别给我那个。 是的。
嗯，我可以做到。 是的。
不。
呃。
发烧。
呃，
（哭泣）
那真是太糟糕了。
呃，
好的。
它。
嗯，
不错。
不，没关系。 我们可以从中恢复过来。
我们可以从中恢复过来。 是的，我们可以
从中恢复过来。
呃，那会
打开它吗？ 可以做到。   是的
。 所以，
我做不到。
嗯，我们去那儿吧。
嗯嗯，就是这个
。
呃，这样
我就能拿到那块绿色区域了。 啊，
没关系。 没关系。 让我们把
银行涂成蓝色。
没关系。 哦，不。
我已经解决了。 我把它清理干净了。 好的。
我确实把它彻底清理干净了。
我的天啊。 决不。 我搞砸了。
决不。 我搞砸了。 我可以
恢复过来。 是的。 是的，
你得好好想想。 我玩这类
游戏很菜。
哦。
哦，不。 不，不，不，不，不，
哦，不。 不不不不不不不不不
啊。
那我这就去做。
所以（哭泣）
然后是“
不”。哦，我搞砸了吗，兄弟？
过来。 过来。 来。
对不起。
因为日本天气冷，我感冒了。
嗯，是的
。
哦，是的。 是的。 我可以康复。 我可以
康复。 我可以康复。
我可以康复。
嗯，是的
，我想要那个。 是的。
我。
呃，那是兄弟。 我可以恢复过来
。 嗯，我一定会这么做的。 他
发烧了。 哦，不。 哦，不。
他发烧了。 哦，不。 不，不，不，
等等。 我可以，我可以，我真的可以。
哦不。
哦，不。
K9。  K9。  K9。  K9。 这很
糟糕。 这很糟糕。 这很糟糕。
呃，
我可以吗？ 不，我无法恢复。 妈的。
Y
mina。
嗯，是的
，我可以，我可以，我可以，
嗯，是的，
我可以，我可以，我可以相信
绿色即将到来。
把它放下来，我就可以做了。
呃，
我本来可能就此止步于此。 这样
可行。 呃，我得把它清理干净。   是的
。 嗯，这样可以。 作品。 作品。
作品。 作品。 把它降下来是好事。
然后，呃，
可以像这样清理干净。
还有那场
发烧。
我们可以这样做。
那是糟糕的部分。 那真是个糟糕的决定。
好的。
哦，不。
嗯，照做就行了。
我可以……嗯，做类似的事情。
拿来。 我正在玩黄色，
嗯，
我可以做到那样做，也可以做到这个。
所以，嗯，
好吧，然后做那边那个红色的东西。
啊，发烧。 好的。 呃，发烧了。 这是发烧。
[哭泣] 我搞砸了。
烧退了。 没关系。 这份工作。
好的。 黄色的。
啊，没关系。 没关系。
我们可以从中恢复过来。
嗯，我可以做到。
我们双手合十，然后说：
没错，这就是我想要的。 然后我们把所有东西都清理干净，
然后再做那件事。
蓝色即将到来。 所以我们可以把它放在
这里。
我们本来可以把它清理干净，不过现在这样也挺好的。   就
这么简单。 红色即将到来。
这
招在那里管用。
呃，
好的。 发烧。 嗯，我们可以做到。   是的
。
好的。
不过，最后时刻的调整还是奏效了。
啊，我搞砸了。
去吧，
我的脖子好痛啊。 我的天啊。 让我躺下休息一下
。   别那样
做。
哦，搞定了
。
这样可行。 这样一来，蓝色就消散了。
我可以做到。 而
大门也
可能赢得牌局的另一半
。
然后我们把它清理干净。
照做。
有几个
蠢货，蠢货，
蠢货。
他妈的。
我的天啊。 我怎么会搞砸了？
我怎么会搞砸了？
是的，我可以做到。 在这个地区。
嗯，
好的，这样可以。
我们可以做到这一点。   把
它清理干净。   把
它清理干净。 那东西要清理干净。 那里也要
清洗干净。
我做不到。 糟了，
我们遇到大麻烦了。
呃，
发烧了。 好的，那就好。
我发烧是件好事。 我觉得我
做不到。
超过。
我搞砸了。  [哭泣]
我当时想，好吧，我可以恢复过来。
这游戏太让人紧张了，
而且好像没完没了。
它会跟着
走。
呃，你
呃，我有玩具，
嗯哼。
呃。
哦，兄弟。 不，我可以把你带回来。 看着
我。
呃。
[哭泣]
呃，兄弟，我坐在长椅上。
糟糕，我坐在长椅上。 他妈的。
我的天哪，太疯狂了。
[叹气]
那真不错。   是的
。 再见。 那么，
Alex，真正的职业选手是什么样的？
这里为什么一个人都没有？ 重放
风格
创建室或
连接。
你好，欢呼特效。 你好，
倒计时结束时自动播放。 是的，
回来助攻。
预测相同。
这是什么？
等等，我为什么要去？ 呃，什么
是集合计数？
设置摇钱树。
呃，
我不知道被
职业选手打败是什么感觉。
糟糕，它显示了我的位置。
是啊，但现在人们都知道我来自
[笑声]我生活得很好。
等等等等。
你好。
哦，
今晚。
等等，为什么没人玩？  [嗤笑] 我
想玩。
为什么没人玩？
好的。
[嗤笑]
为什么没人玩？
是的，
匹配系统又需要队友了。 嗯，
技能等级。
呃，我需要输入房间密码。
我该怎么做？ 我怎么才能知道
我的房间密码之类的信息？
返回
收藏。
好的。 我会取消订单。 哦，有人来了
。 有人在海外服役。
呃，D，我想和格蕾丝·J一起去。
好吧，是时候看我被打败了。   我的
天，是魔法积木！
但
我认为我会模仿他。 我不
知道。   我的
天，他打得真快。 哦，不。
啊，快速下拉功能没有。 啊，原来如此
。   妈的
。 嗯，这
就是原因。 我的天哪，他
打得太好了。 我的天哪，
我太抱歉了。 呃，
兄弟，我做不到，我做不到，我做不到。
这是
他正在禁食。
我慢慢来。   妈的
。 哦，你的屁股，你的屁股，你的
屁股。
哦，不。
哦，我慌了。
兄弟，[笑声]
兄弟。
兄弟，他屏幕上发生了什么？
Y：
刚才到底发生了什么？  [笑声]
他是不是搞了什么大规模连锁反应？
我的天哪，看看他走得多快。
这就是被比
自己强的人打败的感觉吗？   我的
天，他又派兵了。
敌军。
哦。
哦。 他现在的打法，就像那种
链子一样。
呃，兄弟，别说了。 停止。 停止。 停止。 停止。
停止。 停止。 停止。 停止。 停止。  Br.
兄弟。 兄弟。 寒意。 寒意。 我勒个去
？   我勒个去
？
我不明白。
我玩得太慢了。 看他走得多快。
开始了。
开始了。 我快要死了。 我死了。
[哭泣]
兄弟。
Brother,
he was like, "This guy is not worth it.
V.
What?
Let's go with this guy.
Tokyo. Someone's from Someone from
Tokyo.
Oh god. Japanese players are so pro at
this game. I I can I can I can feel it,
bro. Look at him play. I'm going to get
shit on. Yeah.
N is dead.
The way he's playing systematically like
a pro, it's it's coming to my brain.
Oh no, I'm dead.
Itsyhe
brosy.
It has begun. It has begun. It has
begun. The massacre has begun. Oh, it's
behind. Oh, God. Help me.
Oh my god. What is going on? What the
hell, brother? What the hell?
Oh my lord.
What?
Why?
Let me copy him. Ah shit.
It's
yooy
stop.
I feel like he knows that I'm a easy
target easy player.
Um
a has begun.
Yeah,
bro. What's the point to play? He's
[crying]
Oh my lord.
How do you know how  to play the the way
he plays? just like a pro player. The
way he plays is a pro player. Why?
He knows. Hello.
The way he plays is he knows how the
game game works.
It's
perfect.
Oh, bro. Stop massacring me.
Look at that.
Ah, bro.
Oh my. It we we going more. Okay.
Yeah, I know. I lost three times.
Oh, bro. He started to massacre me.
Mate, mate, mate, mate, mate. I'll
massacre him. I can do this. I can do
this. I can do this. I can do this. I
learned the I learned the tactics. I
learned the tactics. I learned the
tactics. I learned the tactics.
Um, yeah, I learned the tactics. Oh my
god, I'm getting better.
Oh fuck. No.
No. [laughter]
I did.
How?
Wait. Let me copy him. Let me copy what
he's doing.
Uh, he put it like this, right? Okay.
Then he put it like this again. Then he
put this thing like  this. Okay, let me
copy him. He will not. No.
Uh, okay. Where did he put this? Uh,
no. That was wrong. No.
[snorts]
Ah, yada. I did it wrong. No.
Aha, bro. I couldn't copy him in time.
The massacre has started again.
Uh, yada.
Uh,
bro, I've lost
[crying]
Okay. I I actually did a
combo. I I did a combo. I did a combo.
Oh my god. I did a combo.
Am
I am I so
I feel like if I'm being forced to play
with the with this pro player, I will
improve cuz I'll be like in my Oh, I
actually defeated him. Bro,
I actually defeated him. Okay.
Oh my god. Actually defeated him. Oh my
god. Thank you.
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Bro, stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
She's done.
What?
I got cooked. I got cocky. That's why
I got cocky.
Wait,
what am I doing?
Oh shit.
I got cooked.
Ah,
how do you use your brain to think ahead
in time?
Uh
I uh
oh the breath shit.
Let's
go back. Ow.
Ah.
Yeah.
Hen players.
Okay. Okay.
[crying]
[snorts]
This guy is from Tokyo, right?
Ah,
I didn't want to.
Okay, I do that. Maybe this.
Oh, no, no, no. I can put it there. And
then maybe I can put it like this. Uh, I
can put it there. Okay. Maybe that goes
there. And uh, no, I didn't want to
shit.
Uh, I can go there. And uh,
that works. Okay. Uh, yeah. He's uh,
he's he's attacking. He's attacking.
He's attacking.
Uh yada yada yada yada.
I can block him maybe.  Uh maybe maybe
bro.
Nah.
How do I How do I do emotes?
Is it Is it going to go forever?
Oh my god. It's gonna go. I mean, it's a
good practice [music] dish.
Getting cooked every single time like
this.
It feels not [laughter] It doesn't feel
bad.
Got the shield.
Yeah. I didn't want to
Oh my god, he's attacking me strong.
I'm kind of understanding that you're
not supposed to chain it in the early
stage. You're supposed to do it in the
medium middle stage.
Oh my god, I died.
At least I got one win. Okay.
Yep.
I'll move only when he had Oh shit.
Uh
Jokix, you're too late.
[crying]
Yes, I defeated him. Let's go.
Oh my god, too. Okay.
Uh, so you have to just match the
colors.
This is good training, by the way. I'm
glad I got a pro Japanese player.
Okay, I almost Oh shit,
he's  uh he's on attacking.
Then I'm going to attack him. Knee.
I need one more. Come on. Come on. Come
on. Come on. Come on. Yes.
Yes. No. No. I was so close.
[crying]
[snorts]
Back to lobby.
H.
Thank you for Oh, he left. Fuck.
I got cooked. How did I Wait, this guy
is still here.
Everyone margin
rate three.
Will he play with me?
Hi.
This ranked in this game.
You can compete in the leaderboards. Oh,
it's Sonic.
Oh shit, I didn't mean to do that. Okay.
Taa.
Ah, that was so dumb.
Oh, it has begun. It has begun. It has
begun.
It has begun. Oh god.
Don't worry.
I'm going to get you, bro.
Uh, he's he's going to go on attackive.
Oh shit. I still have a chance. I still
have a chance.
Still have a chance.
I still have a chance.
Give me right. Give me right.  Yes. Yes.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Yes.
I've improved, brother. Yes.
Yes. Yes.
I did it. I didn't let him combo
mass combo me.
I did not let a mouse combo me.
Oh shit, that was that was dumb. That
was dumb. Okay, jump.
Good.
It's
itsy
I'm defeating him.
Yes. Oh my god.
Um
Oh my god, guys. Are you seeing this?
Yay. Yay. Yay. Yay. Yaba yaba. I'm
getting better.
Are you witnessing
Mina?
Uh,
it's it's
I think this was a mistake.
I shouldn't have cleaned it out. I
shouldn't have cleaned it out. Gosh,
that was a mistake. He He got He got
this round.
He got this run.
Oh, he got this run. I was early. I was
early.
Oh shit. Fuck.
Nice job, bro.
Uh
yeah. Hey
Bro, what am I doing?
Don't let him  combo. Don't let him
combo. Do not let him combo.
Do not let him combo.
If you let him combo, you're dead.
Ah.
Shinda shinda.
I let him combo.
H. Oh god. Oh god. I
The way looks like I think I'm going to
die.
Yeah,
black.
It's
Don't overshoot it.
You can now.
I will shoot him. Yeah,
it's fine. Do it.
Do it.
No. Oh, wait. I think I got it. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
No.
This guy is so strong.
Seven chains.
He left.
Am I the only one here?
Hello, welcome
worldwide.
Just dropping by here
by all.
What are you uh what is this game about?
It's It's like Tetris but with a with
like some cute characters.
Yeah, it's literally [music] Tetris and
Candy Crush. Similar to that you
um
match color match actually stuff and do
it.
So there is a tournament hosted by Vak
India on 18th of October  on a Sunday at
7:30 p.m. ISG. So I'm participating in
that tournament. So I'm like um
practicing
for this.
Yeah.
I know it is here.
We put broadcast to
Can we watch other people?
Let's watch this guy.
Is it recording though?
Look at these guys. The way they are
playing though.
pop to make a fortune.
Look at him play.
How do you know where to target
the prediction though?
Is it?
Oh my
good lord.
guy's a pro.
There's a prediction thingy on
there. That's a prediction thingy on.
That's why I think
I kind of old time, huh?
I kind of understood.
I'll explain the CP version.
Um,
is there anyone here? Wait,
someone is here in the room.
Oh,
someone from Ku
Japan.
Holy lord. That's a
I've been krah.
He kicked me. What the hell,
bro? He kicked me.
What the hell?
He That guy kicked me. The hell did I do
to him?
I going to
uh And
there are no people in the fever.
Oh.
Oh shit.
Tik Tok. Someone from Tik Tok. [snorts]
Yuru. It's a Japanese brother.
It's
quick.
Or should I die?
It's it's
it's
Itsy
itsy.
Oh no.
It's
Oh shit.
Oh, no.
It's It's
It's
no
He got free points. Rang up.
Oh, my rating went down. Shit.
Fore!
Foreign!Foreign!
Yahoo!
It's
not
Bro, what the hell?
Oh my lord,
I died.
I have to defeat him. How
Uh
it's
Itsyhe
It's
shit.
It's It'sy.
No. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
I just need a It's one v one. No. One
one.
Oh god. He's He's speeding up. He's
speeding up. Yono
quiet.
Oh god,
he's sending threats at me. Oh lord.
It's
a bro.
Brother  in Christ.
Brother in Christ.
He
my rating is lowered.
I don't want to play with him.
The hell
filters.
Oh my god.
Oh my, I just played with the top top
number four player in the world.
A grandmaster
who just No, no. Earlier the Gohan guy
was the grandmaster. Oh my god.
How do you say it?
Okay,
replay is the best.
Yeah,
it's secret.
It's
Oh shit.
I didn't even fuck
It's great.
Itsy
item.
Oh no.
Ah,
he won.
One more.
Oh no. What?
Oh shit.
Broch.
These players are crazy
and I'm having a really bad cold.
It's weather. The weather is so cold,
too.
Stop sending threats,
bro.
No.
Hello, Vic. Oh my god, it's Dick. Hello.
How are you doing?
It's been a while.
How you doing, Rick?
I couldn't do that. Okay.
Uh
oh, he's sending attacks at me. Oh.
Oh my god. Wait. I don't know.
Uh,
please,  please, please, please.
No. [crying]
Um
what idle stuff and then I'm fine. This
is okay.
We also doing well. It's uh cold over
here.
What's the weather in Japan right now?
20°.
Cold.
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
[crying]
He dropped me.
Ah, he dropped it.
Connection. I think he all that Ford.
What the hell? He's like, I don't want
to play with the newbie.
I need to learn how the game and play
the game.
Let's watch this
tutorial.
Hi
Ready?
Special controls.
Even faster way to drop your sensor is
basically
they call this quick drop.
Jesus.
This is the chain and they send me the
keys to mushroom field.
I just score a chain score more points.
I found the jeans also some go
up to disappear James
T.
Oh,
simultaneous clear. Oh,
neutralizing.
We call this new choice.
What do you do?
I put that. Oh, okay.
You can neutralize them before.
Oh.
Oh,
okay. That is neutralizing.
Quick one
wrong. If you quickly press  the right
person ZX control key twice can rotate
the P.
Oh,
interesting.
It is false.
You can score bonus points. Oh,
saving up chains.
couple of few pure drops ending up here
for easy chains. Okay.
Okay.
Huh.
That's the end of the intermediate.
Creating multiple chains is the key,
too.
Oh, bro. This is so hard.
Okay,
come on this side.
Wait,
is there no one else playing this game
today?
If there people playing, I would want to
play and battle them.
I have to learn how to do this. Bro, at
this point, I don't think I can
win the tournament or the team. I will
be a disappointment for my team. I mean,
and this is day one though. But I think
I just have to keep on playing and
playing and um understand
the game.
We'll eventually get it.
Um,
one second. Let me check. Uh,
if anyone from
is anyone I know streaming
dish
like
Oh, wait. As first room filming.
Oh, wait. What time is it for people?
Ah, it's 8:00 p.m.  for them. Um, it's 12
for me. I forgot Japan time and Indian
time is
uh different
times on
most people get uh start their stream at
10 or 9.
Little battle.
Learn to make chains. That's the
victory. That's the goal to victory.
Learn to make chains. Talk next.
Got to make them chains.
Uh,
Oh shit.
Oh, no. No, no, no. I I was trying to
combo. Come on. I was trying to
I was trying to combo.
chat.
See if you
Interesting.
Shit.
Itsy
didn't do it.
Uh
something like uh
I'm not trying I I'm not supposed to try
to clear it. I'm supposed to build up
chains. Don't forget
build up chains. Dark legs.
Yes. Keep going.
Keep going. Learn how to build up
chains. That's how you'll
understand.
Uh
uh. What the
I need space.
I can defeat him. Yeah.
Yeah. That's how you do legs. Yeah.
Good, good, good,  good, good. Yeah.
Yeah. Slow and steady wins the race
slowly.
Surely
I'll try to play this game tomorrow. No,
not tomorrow. I want to play some FPS
tomorrow. Yeah, I'll try to play this
game on weekends.
Uh, no, on weekdays.
Oh, yeah. Monday I don't have class.
Yeah. Uh, so I can find some time. I
need to find some time to tournament.
Oh no. Oh, he's attacking. He's
attacking.
Let me just kill him fully.
I'll just kill him.
Okay, good. Oh my god. I And I I learned
[music] the game. No, wait. No, no.
Don't be cocky.
Take it slow.
Oh shit.
Could have fuck
it.
I can actually do it.
It's about doing, you know, I'm not
supposed to do it early.
Feel like I'm doing the early combos,
which is bad. I have to wait for my
opponent.
Yeah, I'm trying to do a early
stuff that is wrong.
Oh my god,  my
uh
Oh god, he got in.
Okay.
It's
slow and steady.
Itsy.
Oh shit.
No.
[crying]
Oh, I might have messed up.
I made a mess up.
Okay, I think we can do one last game
and I can wrap up. It's It's going to be
It's It's 1 It's going to be 12:30.
Yeah, I
I know I could keep on playing, but um
yeah,
sure. I know tomorrow is a Sunday.
And yeah, for those who don't know, I
Well, I think I didn't tweet. Oh, I
forgot. So, um, for those who didn't
know, my cycle got stolen recently.
So, I'm buying a new cycle bicycle
tomorrow
at 10 in the morning. Um, so after I get
my cycle and stuff, I think I'll start
streaming.
Um, I'm thinking of streaming. Um
um
the thing is when during weekends,
right, I won like some have like a
shooter game. I need my FPS pew  pew.
But lately I've been pew pewing so much,
right?
So, I was thinking
um I was thinking I could uh go with
either this game for like 6 hours, six
or eight hours.
Not that long, but it's a Sunday, so
might have to go out to buy stuff
[gasps]
uh and stuff. I I don't I do not know my
schedule for tomorrow. I don't even
think I can do like more than 4 hour
shrimp, but
even at nights I my roommate
uh and I we um he will help prepare the
dinner and
uh by 9 or 10 I I'll get free if he is
going to
uh go sleep early.
So,
um
I could stream from 10 like today's
stream from 10 to 12,
but
yeah, short streams are pain.
[snorts]
Also, I just noticed
I noticed something.
The game goes quiet when you are all
tabbing.
Why is it that?
Why is it like that?
It was windowed.
Does it act the same? Ah, it does.
Uh,
wait. Why is it like that? Oh,
wait. Why is it like that?
Why is it like that?
Okay. Is there a way I could
Let me check. uh for you for your
champions
game.
Is there a way to
uh
when I'm not
focused?
Uh mute window lo
and focus loss is actually for the game.
Uh,
is there a way I could
do something?
Um,
virtual desktop.
No, it
it's doesn't
have audio on
wireless.
Wait
full screen windowed to how do I make it
like have audio
has a hardcoded for mute build directly
in the game engine. Oh.
[sighs and gasps]
Uh
uh
audio routing cable. No,
I mean it's fine I guess if it's silent,
right?
Uh
there is a auto hotkey
uh script for this.
I can make it think I am focused on it.
that way. There is still audio,
but I'm worried if I get cuz this is a
this game has esports and stuff
apparently,
competitions  and stuff. So, I'm like
thinking like
is it safe for me to do that?
I know.
Um
we p
How about that?
Let me do something. One second.
Okay. Wait.
Uh,
how do I
Oh shit. Wait, how do I run this?
Uh,
loading. Okay.
Oh, wait, wait, wait. I fixed it. Oh my
god. Okay. Auto hotkey. Thank you. So,
I'm I'm literally not focused on the
game, but
uh the game thinks I'm focused on it,
but I'm not. That way you can you guys
on stream can hear the audio. It
wouldn't sound like I'm all tabbing.
That is nice.
That is actually nice.
We figured out something. He
get qui.
Uh, no.
Uh. Oh, full screen doesn't work. Oh,
isn't this like a old game?
So for [music] screen optimization when
Oh yeah, that will
is it me or when I put it on 1080p
the stuff looks blurry.
Or is it just me? Why does the  text and
everything looks blurry?
Hey,
Wait, am I?
Yeah, this is clear. This is clear.
Clear. Clear. Okay,
watch this.
[snorts]
Hey, switch to this. It's start going to
start becoming blurry. Okay.
See, it's blurry.
It wor.
And why?
Why though?
Hey, why does it do that?
Hey,
wait. Alt enter. No, no, wait.
Wait, wait, wait. What was the command?
Control enter. No, hold
alt enter.
Ah, it forces forced.
Hey, why is it blurry though?
Why is it blurry though?
Oh, that is so weird.
If it's blurry like this, can't I like
go to in game files and like
uh is it not something like that? No,
nothing
like config something. Uh no. Okay, it
doesn't have it.
Yeah.
Yep. They do not have it, it seems.
Why was same games?
Oh, [snorts]
usually it's supposed to be there in the
save folder or something.
Uh,
I can't find it.
Wait, Sega, right? So, let's see.
Oh, it's over here. Wow.
What the
local?
Oh, it's Sega S
or P Pew Pew.
Oh, yes.
Config
file. Okay.
With the game just Okay.
Okay. Graphics config. [music]
Oh,
[sighs] okay. Okay. So, what it'll do is
1920 by
full screen one go one full screen width
of V6 one and uh
save this and
save this and right click and
mark as read Finally apply
quit to desktop
and I'll launch the game again.
And it should now give me uh 1080p
quality on a window at full screen
if I'm correct.
Yes.
Oh my god, I'm a genius.
No, it's not nothing about genius or
anything. It's just what it is there out
there for other games.
See, it's not blurry anymore. The boxes.
All right, there is a little bit of
blurriness. You see  the ones over here?
One, one X.
Oh no. Is it that blurry?
It's not that blurry.
It's not that blurry, so it's fine.
Anyone know?
Uh let's uh
let us
wrap up. I guess
I can't
for tonight.
It is late.
Titan.
Uh I
will continue in the next PP stream.
Okay.
Uh let me switch to the game scene. I
know talking scene.
My nose is blocked. Oh god, I've been
sneezing.
on stream and off stream. We have about
while muted the I muted the mic and was
sneezing so much.
It is
but yeah. Um
I I just want to say that like I
I'll be streaming more of this game. I
need to get used to
um used to the game and learn how to do
the uh chains and everything.
Uh, that would mean I have to use my
brain a lot,
but it's a fun game. It gives you like a
uh
it may it trains your brain to think
which colors can which pattern can  go
well with this. Why? How should you
place the placement of the block? Uh the
pu or blocks. It's literally Tetris you
can say. Yeah. The more I play this
game, I feel like I should
try to play by one day play sandress
or something. There's a sand tress
thingy that's also similar like this.
It's fun.
You can
uh you know match the colors and
make them
chain attack all those stuff.
Same stuff like neutralization and quick
quick move quick
stuff like that. I just really
interesting.
Um,
forgot my phone notifications.
Yeah,
a second.
Uh,
but yeah, today was fun. And I
got to
try out this game finally. Apparently
now uh everyone who are participating in
the tournament from India uh most of
them it's the game is like 250
rupees or something because of the 50%
off going on for this game on Steam for
the autumn sale.
So, since I'm in Japan, due to a
regional difference, uh the tournament
organizers organizers, they uh  tried to
send me the free game copy cuz I'm a
participant, but they couldn't gift me.
I couldn't accept the gift because of
the regional thingy.
Apparently, if you didn't know, like on
Steam, they do allow cross region
gifting, but the issue is more like
if a game has regional restrictions.
For example, this game is from Sega,
right? Yeah. So, Sega had regional
restrictions for this game. That's why
um
it it defaulted uh the Steam uh yeah if
a game publisher has regional uh
limitations
uh restrictions like that it will
default
back to the old thingy. Uh so you cannot
do cross gifting
or something. That's what let me when I
asked like
to in Google search it just said me that
apparently someone talked about this in
like for other games and also some
somewhere in Reddit I guess. I'm not
sure but yeah that happened. So, I was
given like a gift card,
the 640 yen gift card since in uh this
game in Japan is like 720
yen.
That's like in Indian 卢比大概是
500卢比左右[音乐]
600卢比，是
你平时能买到的东西的两倍
m 印度售价约 250 卢比。
[嗤之以鼻] 为什么日元这么贵？
我不太明白
。 太多了。 你知道吗？
今天
我的自行车不能骑了，
后轮好像不行了，好像
是打孔之类的，
在日本换个轮胎内胎要6000日元，
就像在印度那样。
如果你需要换轮胎或
内胎之类的，价格应该在
2000到1000日元之间。 低于 1000 美元。
不会超过这个数。
6000日元约合
3.7，
四舍五入后约为3700
卢比。   真是疯了
。 不，它收取了大约
7000的服务费。 哦，是的。
愚蠢的服务费。 是的，4300
卢比。 真是疯了。 疯狂的。
我不知道该说什么。
不过这里什么都贵。
天哪，我的孩子们也是。
过来。
我必须更安静些。
因为我得安静些，所以我的室友们都在睡觉
。   是的
。
所以，嗯
，我会
告诉你们我
明天要直播什么内容。 好的，就先这样吧
。
谢谢你今天抽出时间。 呃，哦
，我的鼻子堵住了。 闷。 我勒个去
？   是
啊，但
我那边也搞砸了。 我的天哪。 你可以
从我的声音里听出来。 我的天哪。   是
啊，但是
天哪，我的鼻子堵住了。 我的天哪。   我的
天哪。
我喘不过气来。 是的。   我的
哎，我的网络快断了。
互联网。
天哪，我的网络又出问题了。
我还活着吗？
是的，你们晚点两
分钟。
好了，我想我今天就到此为止吧
。 抱歉，我一直在打喷嚏。
好的，我这边就到此为止了。
我打喷嚏打个不停。
等待。   是的
，情况越来越糟了。 我
打喷嚏打个不停。 是的。
请允许我谈谈我的上帝。
好的。 天哪，我都说不出话来了。
他（音乐）每说一秒钟，我一张嘴，
就打喷嚏。
好的。 再次感谢
今天到场的各位。 让我念一下你们的名字。
谢谢你，维克多。
谢谢你，阿拉萨。 谢谢。
谢谢。
谢谢你，玛雅，过来玩。
那么，嗯，艾丽森，谢谢你
过来。 罗恩，谢谢你过来。
谢谢光临。
还有
所有那些
在 YouTube、Twitter
和 Rumble 上潜水的潜水员们。 非常感谢
观看直播。 这对我
意义重大。   是的
。 再见。
我的嗓子快要哑了。
所以，再次感谢各位的
光临。 下次我还会继续直播
。 我会在 Discord、
Twitter 或 Instagram 快拍之类的平台上通知大家
。 是的。
你好。
嗯，我觉得我生病了。 我得吃点
药。 呃，这可糟了。 天气
越来越冷了。 嗯，
是的，我讨厌冬天，但冬天也挺好的。   是
啊，我讨厌感冒。
我喝了点热水什么的。   是
啊，这太糟糕了。 是啊，不过还是要
再次感谢你。 祝
大家一切顺利。 祝你今晚睡个好觉。
再见。
我的天哪